export const musicQuestions = [
    
    {
        question: "Which part of New York is the Hip Hop group Wu-Tang Clan from?",
        options: ["Staten Island", "Brooklyn", "Queens", "Harlem" ],
        correctAnswer: "Staten Island"
    },
    
    {
        question: "Who wrote the song Bad? (Relased 1987)",
        options: ["Elvis", "Adele", "Billy Joel", "Michael Jackson"],
        correctAnswer: "Michael Jackson"
        
    },
    
    {
        question: "Who is a member of The Beatles?",
        options: ["George Michael", "Eminem", "Mark Knofpler", "Ringo Starr" ],
        correctAnswer: "Ringo Starr"
    },
    
    {
        question: "What year was Blur's album Parklife released?",
        options: ["1998", "2001", "1972", "1994"],
        correctAnswer: "1994"
    },
    
    {
        question: "How many studio albums have Taylor Swift released?",
        options: ["10", "18", "5", "11" ],
        correctAnswer: "11"
    },
    
]

export const bookQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who wrote the Harry Potter Books?",
        options: ["Alfred Nobel", "J.K. Rowling", "George Orwell", "Franz Kafka"],
        correctAnswer: "J.K. Rowling"
    },
    {
        question: "When was the first Nobel Prize awarded?",
        options: ["1892", "1924", "2001", "1901"],
        correctAnswer: "1901"
    },
    {
        question: "Who wrote the famous quote: To be, or not to be?",
        options: ["Erik Carr", "William Shakespear", "Charles Dickens", "T.S. Eliot"],
        correctAnswer: "J.K. Rowling"
    },
    {
        question: "How many books/novels has Stephen King written?",
        options: ["29", "15", "98", "65"],
        correctAnswer: "65"
    },
    {
        question: "Who turned the Lord Of The Rings books in to movies?",
        options: ["Cristopher Nolan", "Peter Jackson", "Quention Tarantiono", "Martin Scorsese" ],
        correctAnswer: "Peter Jackson"
    },
    
]